export const CardData = [
  {
    id: '1',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'Flip Me',
    back: 'Match phrases in different languages',
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'Foo',
    back: 'Bar',
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'Apple',
    back: 'Tree',
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'Father',
    back: 'Papi',
  },
  {
    id: '5',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'fnfnw',
    back: 'f9f9w',
  },
  {
    id: '6',
    variant: 'click',
    front: '[]',
    back: 'Array',
  },
  {
    id: '7',
    variant: 'click',
    front: '() => {}',
    back: 'es6 function',
  },
  {
    id: '8',
    variant: 'click',
    front: 'def my_function()',
    back: 'Python function',
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    variant: 'click',
    front: '{x.n}',
    back: 'Object',
  },
  {
    id: '10',
    variant: 'click',
    front: '===',
    back: 'Strict equals',
  },
];
